This is a Hangman game with all the required features implemented.
The window is resizable, so when it is scaled, all interface elements scale and reposition accordingly.
The words are read from a txt file, where comma is the delimiter.
All whitespaces are removed by parsing, just the spaces between separate words in a single name remain.

Eight mistakes instead of seven. The additional one is added for pushing the step away from hangman, thus having more "spectacular death" with animations :)

On mobile devices landscape view is recommended.

Use npm install, then:

npm start 

for test, or:

npm run build-prod 

for production



Boyan Taksirov

www.blite.eu